<Sequence>
	<DisplayName>Tutorial</DisplayName>
	<Description>
		Prove yourself to earn your guild membership the quick way.
		You need to demonstrate mastery of previous magical knowledge by obliterating dummies.
		Afterwards you will solve a puzzle that tests your analytical skills and to finish up 
		you will brew a simple potion. Don't worry. You paid the fees in time, thus we will make this easy.
	</Description>

	
	<Soundtrack>Lightless Dawn.mp3</Soundtrack>
	
	<Reward>Mages_Certificate</Reward><!--Unlock this thing for the player. It allows accessing additional sequences-->
	<RewardHuman>Mage Certificate</RewardHuman>
	<RewardIcon>../Data/2D/Rewards/Mage_Certificate.png</RewardIcon>
	
	<CompleteRequirement>Mages_Certificate</CompleteRequirement><!--Usually one of the rewards!-->
		
		
	<Art3D>
		<ModelFile>../Data/3D/LabyrinthParts/Target.obj</ModelFile>
		<TextureFile>../Data/2D/Blue.png</TextureFile>
		<Transform>
			<RotX>0</RotX>
			<Scale>1.00</Scale>	
		</Transform>			
	</Art3D>	
	
	<Entry>
		<Intro>
			<Heading>Spell Choice</Heading>
			<Text>
				Examiner: In this simplest of all tests you will take on one of our patented target dummies.
				It features a basic magical defense, though it pales against that of even the simpelst living creature.
				Ready a spell or two and pummel the dummy with it.
				As this is your main interest, you know all four spell bases of the arcane school:
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Mola: A searing, volatile outburst of fire that is easy to guide.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Vex: An arcing lightning bolt. A glorious flash or a fizzle out 
				at the slightest slipup.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Sal: A devastating spell that drains victims of their body warmth and crystallizes incorporeal entities.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Vita: Known only to the bloodwitches, this spell drains life itself from the victim. 
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Each spell behaves differently when it comes to bypassing enemy defence.
			</Text>
		</Intro>
		<Fight>
			<Condition>
				<Type>ExactName</Type>
				<StringValue>Tutorial1</StringValue>
			</Condition>
			<Stage>../Data/Stages/Tutorial.xml</Stage>
		</Fight>
	</Entry>
	
	<Entry>
		<Intro>
			<Heading>Spell Choice</Heading>
			<Text>
				Examiner: Behold: The armor dummy, tried and true. 
				Many would be mages despair when faced with the complexity of it's defenses.
				Or when their spells barely glance the fortified shell of infused granite.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				In addition to having different behaviour, spells also have different effects aside from damage. 
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Mola: Every labyrinth pickup (blue) will grant an additional random effect.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Vex: Reduce enemy spell points, inhibiting their special abilities.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Sal: Will always stun enemy if no countermeasure is hit (see frozen stun bar). 
				Sal also deals icnresed base damage.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Vita: Directly steal lifeforce and add it to your pool.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Choice of the correct spell is as important as proper execution. 
				A suboptimal spell flawlessly executed may still be mediocre.
				Some labyrinths may be much easier with a certain spell.
			</Text>
		</Intro>
		<Fight>
			<Condition>
				<Type>ExactName</Type>
				<StringValue>Tutorial2</StringValue>
			</Condition>
			<Stage>../Data/Stages/Tutorial.xml</Stage>
		</Fight>
	</Entry>
	
	<Entry>	
		<Intro>
			<Heading>Enemy Abilities</Heading>
			<Text>
				Examiner: The combats trial ends here! For most participants anyway. Our spellcaster dummy is one of the most sophisticated 
				magical machines and may push your endurance to breaking point.
				Actually if you beat this one, it is also the end of the combat trial.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				So far hitting countermeasures has been fairly consequence-free aside from disabling stun.
				However for each you hit a part of the spell's energy is transmitted to it's would-be victim
				in the form of spell points. 
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Most enemies in the game can spend spell points on abilities much more powerful than their regular attacks.
				Avoid building up spell points on enemies, or at least don't let them live to make your life hell.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				The upcoming fight can be beaten in a variety of ways.
				If you haven't yet tried all four spells, this would be a good opportunity.
			</Text>
		</Intro>
		<Fight>
			<Condition>
				<Type>ExactName</Type>
				<StringValue>Tutorial3</StringValue>
			</Condition>
			<Stage>../Data/Stages/Tutorial.xml</Stage>
		</Fight>
	</Entry>
	

	<Entry>	
		<Intro>
			<Heading>Analysis</Heading>
			<Text>
				Examiner: What? You thought being a mage consisted only of blowing stuff to bits?
				Here take this puzzle box and write me a report on the subject visualized in it's vault. 
				You ... know how to write, I hope?
			</Text>
			<Text>
				No stress. You can't die while analyzing something. Though it has happened before to certain extremely dedicated analysts.
				You can try as many times as you want.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Actually, still stress. In an analysis sequence you need to solve a puzzle before time runs out.
				Theres two ways to go about such an endavour, differing only in ther in-labyrinth behaviour.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Intuition: High speed. A vital asset in time limited situations.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				Abstraction: Teleport to the start when touching countermeasures instead of having to start over. 
			</Text>
		</Intro>
		<Fight>
			<Type>Analysis</Type>
			<Condition>
				<Type>ExactName</Type>
				<StringValue>Tutorial4</StringValue>
			</Condition>
			<Stage>../Data/Stages/TutorialAnalysis.xml</Stage>
		</Fight>
	</Entry>
	
	<Entry>	
		<Intro>
			<Heading>Analysis</Heading>
			<Text>
				You finish your essay on the usage of wyvernroot in folk medicine well on time.
				As the pupil of a with this is nothing to you. With ample time left you call for the examiner.
				No one answers. You try the door, but it's locked.
			</Text>
			<Text>
				It is an unusual door indeed. Some magical mechanism guards it instead of a lock.
				Figuring this is your final test you set to work.
			</Text>		
		</Intro>
		<Fight>
			<Type>Analysis</Type>
			<Condition>
				<Type>ExactName</Type>
				<StringValue>Tutorial5</StringValue>
			</Condition>
			<Stage>../Data/Stages/TutorialDoorBackground.xml</Stage>
		</Fight>
	</Entry>
	
	

	
</Sequence>
	
